翻譯: sumsmit
好吧 Stuart 新規矩
Ok, Stuart, new ground rule.
從今天起 每當我有朋友過來
From now on, whenever I have friends over,
校對: los los los
你都不能帶女孩兒回家
you cannot bring a girl home.
饒了我吧 那才是第一次約會
Give me a break. It was a first date.
我也感覺挺別扭的
I was feeling uncomfortable, too.
后期: 東仔
你當然別扭了
Of course, you were feeling uncomfortable.
她張開四肢扒在你身上
She rode you in on all fours.
壓制: 猴給力
這得怪我
That was my fault.
是我太調皮了
I had been very naughty.
幫個忙好嗎
Do you guys mind?
寫作可是我一生的夢想
It's been a lifelong dream of mine to do real writing.
我終于能有機會寫一些東西
I've finally been commissioned to do a piece
投稿給全國聞名的雜志社
for a respected national magazine.
真的么 <紐約客>還是<名利場>
Oh, really? The new yorker? Vanity fair?
<輕狂>
Sassy.
昨天就是截稿日了
Any way, the article was due yesterday,
能不能靜一靜 各位
so if I could get some peace and quiet, gentlemen.
你竟然在約會的事兒上找我麻煩
Can't believe you'd hassle me over a date.
你看我就從來都不抱怨
You don't see me complaining
昨晚你的狗咬我的床柱
that dog chewed up my bedpost last night.
Stuart昨晚Rags一直在獸醫那兒
Stuart, Rags spent the night in the vet.
我得給那妞回電話
I've gotta call that girl back.
她真輕狂
She-e-e-e's sassy!
政界小人物
第三季 第二十一集
電波誠譯
抱歉 我來晚了
Sorry I'm late.
市長 你今天的安排很緊
Sir, you've got a full day ahead of ya.
9:00到10:45預算會議
We start with a budget meeting from 9:00 to 10:45,
緊挨著就是空氣質量管理的研討會
rocket into a symposium on air quality management,
就在你以為自己不能再亢奮下去時 嘣
and when you think you can't take any more excitement, bam!
又有四個多小時的預算會議
4 more hours of budget meetings.
我有沒有告訴你們我爺爺去世了
Did I tell you guys that my grandfather died?
昨晚嗎
Last night?
30年前
30 years ago.
但這讓我想到
But it got me thinking.
我們一生花了太多精力在工作上
So much of our lives are spent focused on work.
我們從不停下腳步
We never stop and connect
和那些人生中重要的人相處下
with the people who are truly important to us.
你爸的電話
Sir, your dad's on the phone.
就說我不在
I'm not here.
我們稍微停一停 來談談我們的
Let's take a minute and let's talk about our...
私人生活
Personal lives.
Paul 就從你開始吧
Paul! Get us started.
我的精子沒有活性
I have non-motile sperm.
老天 還有30秒Doug的觀光團就要到了
Oh, God. T-minus 30 seconds to tour guide Doug.
Carter 裝做我男朋友吧
Carter, act like my boyfriend.
抱歉 我沒時間
Oh, sorry. I don't have time
去買輛科邁羅然后再疏遠你的父母
to buy a camaro and alienate your parents.
位于我們右邊的是本次游覽的亮點
Coming up on our right is the highlight of our tour.
市政廳的驕傲
The pride of city hall.
Stacey Paterno小姐
Ms. Stacey Paterno.
她好美
She's beautiful.
Doug 你真煩人
Doug, you're annoying
看一眼都讓我反胃
and the sight of you makes my stomach turn.
大家好
Hi, everyone.
Doug 這位是我男朋友
Doug, this is my boyfriend.
是的 還有你們 嗯
Yeah, and you, uh...
都不許看我的女人
Better not be eyeballin' my woman!
各位 這位是Carter Heywood
People, this is Carter Heywood.
他是個出柜的同性戀
He's an avowed homosexual.
還想騙我 真可恥
Shame on you for trying to fool Doug.
可恥啊
Shame.
好的 我們往前
And we're movin'.
那 我們
So, are we...
今晚還有戲嗎
Still on for tonight?
當然了 誰先走
Yeah. Who leaves first?
我先 我出去的時候
I will. On my way out,
我會留一張合同在你桌上
I'll drop a stack of contracts off on your desk.
想讓我十分鐘后裝作很惱火然后走吧
Ok. Then you want me to act annoyed and leave 10 minutes later?
不 完成合同
Oh, no. Finish the contracts.
我之后再去你家
I'll swing by your house later.
聽著 Mike
Hey, listen, Mike.
自打我們在市長辦公室里的談話后
Ever since we opened up to each other in the mayor's office,
我都覺得我們的友誼上了一個新臺階
I think we've taken our friendship to a whole new level.
我也是的 Paul 那你現在可以閃人了嗎
Me, too, Paul. Now you wanna get out of my way?
總之呢 我家的事情有點棘手
Anyway, listen. Things are a little tense at home.
我貌似沒法讓Claudia懷上
I just can't seem to get Claudia pregnant.
每晚 一夜又一夜
Every night, night after night,
她在我背上 騎著我
she's on my back, riding me.
我注意到你的問題了
I think I've zeroed in on your problem.
你知道原因嗎 都是那些該死的懶精子
You know what it is? It's those damn lazy sperm.
他們都不會游泳
They're just lousy swimmers.
也許他們高臺跳水比賽時可以拿分呢
Maybe they'll pick up points in the high dive.
你都不信
And you can't believe the
那些醫生怎么測試的 那個探針 哦喲
tests the doctors gave me. The probing... ooh.
你這些個人隱私
You just barrel ahead with the personal stuff...
他們說是我睪丸的問題
they figured out it was my testicles.
Stacey 紅色警報
Stacey? Code red.
Paul 出去
Paul, get out.
我很感激你 能讓我在你辦公室工作 市長
I appreciate you letting me work in your office, sir.
你不知道在外面干活多難
You have no idea how hard it is to get any work done out there.
我真同情你
I totally empathize.
有時候都不相信我在這兒的效率有那么低
Sometimes I can't believe how little I get done in here.
抱歉啊
I'm sorry.
那啥
You know...
從來沒人來跟我閑聊
No one ever just drops by to chat.
你貌似是個很好的聆聽者
You seem like you're a pretty good listener.
是的 我覺得我可是個帥小子
Yeah, I think I'm a pretty good-looking kid.
我很抱歉 市長 我很樂意聊天 但是我實在是太忙了
I'm sorry, sir, I would love to talk. It's just that I'm so busy.
只希望能安安靜靜的就好
It's nice to have some peace and quiet.
安安靜靜的
Peace and quiet.
安靜
Silence.
安靜喲
Silencio!
Mike 我能雇個實習生么
Hey, Mike, can I hire an intern?
- 不行  - 別這樣Mike 我陷進去了
- No. - Come on, Mike. I'm swamped.
她多大了
How old is she?
18 但你肯定會覺得她25了
18, but you'd swear she's 25.
還是不行
No again.
Mike 明天我能晚來一點嗎
Mike, can I come in late tomorrow?
我要給一個肇事逃逸案件出庭作證
I have to testify in a hit-and-run case.
不行
No.
沒事 他是我一朋友
No problem. I mean, he's a friend of mine,
但他已從昏迷中醒了
but he's out of the coma.
你記不記得你上次說行是什么時候
Do you even remember the last time you said yes?
我覺得這工作讓你變冷血了
I think this job might be making you a cold person.
沒有的事兒
That's not true.
那昨天
Uh-huh. And what happened
有人問你要幾塊錢 你是怎么回答的
when someone asked you for a few dollars yesterday?
我說不給 然后讓他自己去找份工作
I said no and told him to get a job.
Mike 他才8歲
Mike, he was 8.
為他的游行樂隊賣糖果賺錢
Selling candy bars for his marching band.
把我當什么啊 小孩一樣好騙嗎
What was I, born yesterday?
你想要成為那種
Do you wanna be the kind of guy
不管別人問什么 總是說不的人么
who automatically says no to people, no matter what the question?
Mike 幫我個小忙
Mike, quick favor.
我能不能借用你的精子讓我老婆懷孕
Can I use your sperm to impregnate my wife?
行
Yes!
太棒了 謝謝你 老兄
Great. Thanks, buddy.
他剛說什么
What did he say?
這位是Stacey paterno
This is Stacey paterno.
Doug 你過來一下
Doug, get over here.
女士們先生們 如果你認真觀察
Ladies and gentlemen, if you look closely,
你們會發現Doug很開心
you can see Doug's elation.
Doug 你以后導游就別介紹我了
Doug, I want off the tour.
聽著 我明白你想要干什么
Look, I understand what you're trying to do here,
但是你和我 我們沒可能的
but you and I? We're just not gonna happen.
明白么 我們不是一路人
See, we're very different.
我是來自布魯克林的乖女孩兒
I'm a simple girl from Brooklyn
喜歡和自己的家人和朋友呆在一起
who enjoys spending time with her family and friends.
你只是個惱人的極品
And you're an irritating freak.
好吧
Ok...
那啥 各位請繼續往這邊走
Well, let's continue this way, folks,
還有 嗯
and, uh...
出去時小心別踩著Doug破碎的心
Try not to trample on Doug's broken heart as we walk out.
市民朋友們好
Why, hello there, citizens.
呵 呵 呵 這就是市長
Yeah, yeah, yeah. That's the mayor.
我們繼續走
And we're movin'.
你看Mike 我已經給小家伙買了
Look, Mike. I already got the little guy
他的第一個棒球手套
his first baseball glove.
我希望他是左撇子 商場促銷來著
I hope he's a lefty. They were on sale.
聽著 有些事情我得跟你們說一下
Uh, listen. There's something I... I have to tell you guys.
這有點難開口
And it's a little difficult,
我就直說了
so I'm just gonna come out and say it.
幫我說說 Nik
Take it away, Nik.
聽著 各位
Uh, look, guys.
Mike還不想生一個孩子
Mike just doesn't want to bring a child into this world
而且還和自己沒聯系
without being involved in his life.
Mike 你要想介入就可以
Mike, you can be involved as much as you want.
老實說 就你這么害怕承諾的人
To tell you the truth, with your fear of commitment,
我們覺得這對你來說是個好機會
we thought this would be a perfect opportunity for you
來成為家庭一部分
to be part of a family.
這個我不確定
I... I don't know about that.
我是說 我現在也有女朋友
I mean, I'm in a relationship right now.
是么 說的好像能成似的
Oh, yeah, like that's gonna work out.
好的 我可以跟你們聊一下嗎
Ok, can I talk to you guys for a second?
我覺得我得跟你們清楚的解釋一下
I think I need to explain this a little more clearly.
你什么人
Who are you?
你沒看出我們的相似之處嗎
Don't you see the resemblance?
勝利的微笑 色瞇瞇的眼神
The winning smile? The bedroom eyes?
你是我的孩子
You're my kid!
不賴 是吧
Not bad, huh?
你來這兒干嘛
Wh-what are you doing here?
我只是來道謝的
I just came to say thanks.
沒有你 也就沒有我
Without you, I don't exist.
你確實不存在
You don't exist.
合作一點吧 兄弟
Work with me here, pal.
你是在干一件偉大無私的事兒
You're doing a great, selfless thing.
我是在干好事 對吧
I am, aren't I?
看 你明白了
So, you see,
Mike只是想等和他的真愛
Mike just wants to wait and do this with someone
來完成這件事兒
he's really in love with.
是不是Mike
Right, Mike?
Claudia
Claudia...
我參加
I'm in.
我們一起生個孩子吧
Let's make a baby.
什么
What?
老天 Mike
Oh, my God, Mike!
Mike 你愿意幫我生小孩兒我實在是太自豪了
Mike, I can't tell you how proud I am that you're having my baby.
Nikki 跟我說話 行嗎 怎么啦
Nikki, talk to me, ok? What's wrong?
我男朋友就要搞大別人老婆的肚子了
Oh, my boyfriend is impregnating another man's wife.
那 除此之外 還有其他煩心事么
So, other than that, nothing's bothering you?
這大家要是知道這事兒了
Do you know how awkward this is going to be for me
我會多尷尬啊
when people find out about this?
Nikki 你聽我說
Nikki, listen to me.
這件事情我只想
You are the only one I care enough about
和你分享只關心你怎么想
to have shared this information with.
那位是副市長Mike Flaherty
That's deputy mayor Mike Flaherty.
他把精子捐給了新聞發言人Paul Lassiter
He's donating his sperm to press secretary Paul Lassiter.
Nikki Nikki
Nikki... Nikki!
接下來 就是本次觀光的亮點了
And now, for the highlight of today's tour.
好 又要來么
Oh, great. Here we go again?
我干嘛非長這么漂亮
Why do I have to be so hot?
這位
This...
是Janelle Cooper
Is Janelle Cooper.
她的生日是4月23號 金牛座
She was born April 23, a Taurus.
性感的代名詞
Sign of the fox.
吼
Grrr.
Janelle 你竟然觀光介紹Janelle
Janelle. You put Janelle on the tour.
這兒沒什么可看的
Nothing to see here.
我們繼續往前走
And we're moving.
非常好 我好高興
Well, good! I'm glad!
好高興不用出現在你愚蠢的觀光介紹了
I'm glad I'm off your stupid tour!
人們都在稱贊你
Wow. People complimenting you,
給你照相
taking your picture,
告訴你 你有多漂亮
telling you you're beautiful.
就算有一天你覺得自己又丑又累
Even on days when you're feeling ugly and tired,
還是會有人來安慰你的
people come by and make you feel all good about yourself.
這些人有病
They're sick bastards.
好的 我們繼續往前
And we're moving...
別這樣 Doug 我可是市長啊 天吶
Come on, Doug. I'm the mayor, for God's sake.
Nikki 你能過來一下嗎
Nikki? Could you come in here for a sec?
Flaherty先生 我有點忙 有活干
Actually, Mr. Flaherty, I'm a bit busy here, doing some work.
這事是跟工作相關的
This is work-related.
我們要討論籌款的計劃
We're discussing fund-raising schedules.
好吧
Fine.
話說回來 在討論那事兒之前
However, before we do that,
我想花一點時間 談論一下
I'd just like to take one moment to, uh, talk about...
我的精子
My sperm.
我說話經常都是這樣開頭的
How many conversations have I started that way?
我要走了
I'm leaving.
Nikki 聽著 大伙
N-Nikki, look. Everyone...
這事很好 這事兒我只有好處
This is great. I mean, I get all the benefits of having a kid,
沒有任何的壞處
with none of the drawbacks.
難道大家都覺得Mike做的是對的嗎
Don't you guys think that what Mike is doing is wrong?
實際上 這一次我站在Mike這邊
Actually, I'm with Mike on this one.
總有一天 我會想要個孩子
Someday, I'm gonna want to have a child,
我也需要一些幫助
and I'm gonna need some help.
需要一些卵子 一個子宮 一個胎盤
I'm gonna need an egg, a uterus, a womb...
總之 一個女人
Well, a woman.
我真不敢相信你這么遲鈍
I can't believe you would be so insensitive
看女人只看器官
as to reduce a woman to her body parts...
卻沒提到胸部
And not even mention the yabbos.
等一下Carter 你這次站Mike這邊嗎
Wait a minute, Carter. You're taking Mike's side on this?
你別煩他了 Nikki
Leave him alone, Nikki.
Mike又沒有女朋友什么的
It's not like Mike has a girlfriend or anything.
對 可能有些蕩婦會跟他交往
Sure, he might have some floozy on the side
他還不好意思跟別人講
who he's too embarrassed to tell anyone about,
但是 說不定她太笨了想不到這點
but, hey, she's probably too dumb to care.
你完成了沒
Ya finished?
- 實際上 市長  - 好極了 休息啦
- Actually, sir...  - Great. Time for a break.
可能還有一會兒 市長
Maybe in a little while, sir.
好吧
I hear ya.
反正我還有點事兒要做
I've got something to do, anyway.
哦 市長 真是太好了
Oh, sir, that's fantastic.
財 富 大 轉 盤
Wheel... Of... Fortune!
是猜一個物品啊
Oh, it's a thing.
鉛筆
Um, pencil.
甘草精
Uh... Licorice.
醬油
Soy sauce.
市長 他們還沒開始呢
Sir, they haven't turned any letters yet.
我知道 這樣更有挑戰性
I know. It's harder this way.
也許我該換個地方寫
Maybe I should work someplace else.
不 不 不 James 別走 別走
No... no... no, James, I insist, I insist.
我們做工作好兄弟吧
Let's be workin' buddies.
反正我要過一遍這個預算報告
I've gotta go over this budget report, anyway.
公路
"Roads...
4百萬
4 million."
哎呀
Yikes.
我想猜個字謎 是不是 醬油
I'd like to solve the puzzle, pat. Is it... Soy sauce?
看我厲害吧
Who's your daddy?
Paul 我真不敢相信你竟然同意這事兒
Paul, I can't believe you're just letting this happen.
我也不舒服 但是我沒有辦法啊
I'm uncomfortable, but what choice do I have?
你這么說很好 不一定非要找Mike吧
I'm glad you said that. It doesn't have to be Mike.
也不是找Mike這件事
Well, it's not that it's Mike.
不管哪個男的跟我老婆睡我都不舒服
I'd be uncomfortable with any man sleeping with my wife.
跟你老婆睡是什么意思
What do you mean "Sleeping with your wife"?
他只是開車載她去生殖門診而已
He's picking her up and driving her to the fertility clinic.
不 不 這周末我跟Claudia談過了
No, no. Claudia and I discussed
我們沒錢去診所 他們上床就行了
We can't afford that. They're just gonna do it.
什么
What?
哦 是的
Oh, yeah.
試管嬰兒一次就要9000刀
Oh, this in vitro thing, it's like 9,000 bucks a pop.
而且還沒有保證
And there's no guarantees.
這種方法要是沒用的話
This way, if it doesn't work,
最多損失12刀買支蠟燭買瓶蘭姆酒
I'm only out 12 bucks for a candle and a bottle of rum.
你為了省錢就這么給你老婆拉皮條了
You're pimping out your wife to save money?
9000刀吶
$9,000!
聽著 這可不是草率決定的
Look, this isn't some rash decision.
我們咨詢了所有的專家
We've consulted all the experts.
我們做了詳盡的研究
We've done exhaustive research,
我們討論所有的細節
we've discussed every detail.
相信我 我們該考慮的都考慮了
Believe me, we got it covered.
那Mike同意和Claudia睡嗎
And Mike agreed to sleep with Claudia?
我忘記告訴Mike了
I forgot to tell Mike.
- 嗨  - 嗨
- Hey. - Hey.
那啥 我們開始吧
Well, let's do this.
哦 Mike 我們先坐下來聊一聊可以嗎
Oh, Mike, do you mind if we sit for a second and just talk?
好的 沒問題
Yeah, sure.
我真有點不太適應
I'm really not comfortable with...
接下來要做的事情
How we're supposed to do this.
蘭姆酒
Rum?
謝謝
Thanks.
聽著Claudia 要我看
Listen, Claudia, the way I look at this,
不過是兩個人為了創造生命走到一起
we're just two people coming together to create a life.
哦 你說的真好
Oh, that's so beautiful.
別擔心 我自己其實也挺緊張的
And don't worry. I... I'm a little nervous about this myself.
我是說 我以前從來沒做過
I mean, I've... I've never done this before.
真的嗎
Really? Ha ha.
你總是那么趾高氣昂的
The way you strut around,
我真猜不到
I never would have guessed.
但是我上網查過了
But I... I've been checking out the Internet, you know.
我很清楚
And, uh, I think I got a pretty good idea
這事兒該怎么搞
how this is supposed to go.
哦 老天
Oh, dear.
Claudia 我了解的越多
And, Claudia, the more I learn,
越覺得我們三人一起做這件事興奮
the more excited I am about doing it with you and Paul.
Paul不會加入我們的
Oh, Paul won't be joining us.
哦 真掃興
Oh, bummer.
你知道的 因為
You know, 'cause...
他有沒有留下提示什么的
Did he leave directions?
沒他我不知道怎么去到那里
Because without him, I don't know how to get down there.
你到底想讓我干什么
What exactly are you expecting me to do here?
哦 噗
Oh, pffft,
你什么都不用做
you don't have to do anything.
我是說 都讓我來做吧
I mean, I'm going to be doing all the work.
你呢 你就那啥 就行了
You just... you just gotta, you know,
坐在那等著我完事就行了
sit back and wait for me to finish.
有意思 我還以為
Funny. I mean, I just assumed
我要稍微參與一下呢
I'd be participating just a little.
Claudia 給我一本黃色雜志
Oh, no, Claudia. All I need is a dirty magazine
我就可以爽歪歪了
and I'm ready to rock and roll.
我們觀光的下一站是
And the next stop on our tour is...
嗨 Doug
Hey, Doug.
干嘛不把美女帥哥們都帶過來
Why don't you bring all those nice people down here?
Doug 來這邊
Doug, come this way.
你內心還是想過來的
You know you want to.
不Doug 來我這邊
No, Doug. Come here.
Doug 來嘛
Doug, come on.
看起來好像Stacey和Janelle
It seems Stacey and Janelle
都有點需要Doug哦
are a bit too needy for Doug.
幸運的是 Doug最近做出了人生抉擇
Fortunately, Doug has recently made a lifestyle choice.
在你們的左邊是Carter Heywood先生的辦公室
On your left is the office of Mr. Carter Heywood.
他是不是秀色可餐
Isn't he delicious?
Doug覺得Carter像
Doug thinks Carter's all that
薯條一樣可口
and a bag of chips.
沒想到Paul沒告訴你
I can't believe Paul didn't tell you.
沒想到他竟然要讓我跟你上床
I can't believe he wanted me to have sex with you.
幸免于難了是吧
Men have survived the experience.
Claudia 我不是這個意思 聽著
Claudia, I didn't mean that. No. Listen.
如果說我要跟別人的老婆上床
If I was ever gonna have sex with another man's wife,
那也肯定找你
it would definitely be you.
或者Jeff Lyles的老婆
Or Jeff Lyles' wife.
我是說 她就像
I mean, she's like...
我去年夏天和她
I... I spent a weekend with
在漢普頓斯度過了一個周末 老天
her in the Hamptons last summer, and, oh, my God!
Mike
Mike...
她是瑞典人
She's swedish.
瑞典人喜歡赤裸身體
這事兒太荒唐了
Oh, this is so ridiculous.
我還是繼續跟Paul試試吧
I'm gonna just have to keep trying with Paul.
我真的非常非常抱歉
I'm so very, very sorry.
聽著 別沮喪 好嗎
But, listen, don't get down, ok?
你們會成功的
Hey, this'll work out.
我知道 但是如果Paul愿意讓我和你這樣
I know, but if Paul would let me be like this with you,
我是說 他真的關心我多少啊
I mean, how much could he really care about me?
把你的臟手從我老婆身上拿開 你個臭小三
Get your hands off my wife, you home wrecker!
我可沒摸你老婆
I didn't touch your wife.
怎么 她配不上你嗎
Why? She not good enough for ya, huh?
我都跟你說了別穿紫色衣服
I told ya not to wear the purple.
James在么
James?
James 你在嗎
James, you in here?
現在是大轉盤時間了
It's wheel time.
線索是 它是一項活動
The clue is... It's an event.
我 我覺得是土撥鼠日
I... I'm thinking groundhog day
或者割禮
or a bris.
果然是你
It's you.
我的孩子
It's my boy.
而且還跟我愛的女人在一起
And you're here with the woman I love.
這是什么征兆嗎
Is this some kind of sign?
Mike 這位是Bobby Hamilton
Uh, Mike, this is Bobby Hamilton,
會計部Gary Hamilton的兒子
son of Gary Hamilton in accounting.
我要先走了
I'm going to go now.
這人嚇屎我了
That man is scaring me.
粑粑
Daddy!
你還好嗎 Mike
You ok, Mike?
是的 說這么多關于孩子的事兒
Yeah. You know, all this talk about babies,
讓我有點激動呢
it's getting me kinda worked up.
這倒是提醒我 我們下周一起
Which reminds me, let's have dinner next week
跟我的朋友Jeff Lyles和他老婆吃頓飯
with my friend Jeff Lyles and his wife.
你會喜歡她的
You'll like her.
她是個瑞典人
She's swedish.
我懂一點法語
I know a little French.
我們現在就去造人吧
Let's... let's go make a baby right now.
Mike 我服過避孕藥了
Mike, I'm on the pill.
我知道 我這不是情緒上來了么 我又不是白癡
I know. I'm caught up in the moment. I'm not an idiot.
我現在就想要你 就在這兒
I want you right here, right now.
來吧
Take me.
你們兩個好上了嗎
Are you guys dating?
從耶魯畢業后 我在市議會贏得議席
After Yale, I won my first elected office in the city council,
然后做了6年清貧的區長后
and after a 6-year stint as borough president,
我就成了這座偉大城市的市長
I became the mayor of this great city.
我不知道 我只是覺得
I don't know. I just don't think
你不適合做市政廳游覽的講解材料
you're city hall tour material.
我可以炒了你
I can also get you fired.
真的嗎
Really?
我可是很確定哦
I'm pretty sure.
好吧 Doug看明白了
Well, Doug sees your point.
我要搬家
And I'm moving.
電波字幕組 歡迎您的加入
官方網站:www.dbfansub.com
新浪微博:@電波字幕組